Here we go, Upgami, this time with Morning Musume。 23 and Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume。 23 and Rio Sakurai from Morning Musume'23.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MC's. I'm Kitagawa, and I'll be delivering this program. I, Kitagawa, celebrated the 4th anniversary of joining the 15th term on June 22nd, the day of this distribution.
Congratulations. Thank you very much. It really feels as if it was only a few days ago that I joined the group.
I was surprised to see how quickly time flies.
We talk backstage all the time and keep in touch with each other as a group, so I am really looking forward to another year of hard work toward our 5th anniversary.
When I hear about the anniversary, I really feel that it has passed in the blink of an eye.
I, Sakurai, also finished the spring tour, which was my second tour as a soloist, and the concert at the hall was over,
Although this was only my second time as a member of the group, there were some songs that I performed for the first time, and from the middle of this tour, cheering was introduced as a part of the concert, so I will never forget the thrill of hearing the cheers of the fans directly.
I will never forget the feeling of hearing the cheers of the fans.
I remember that it was a lot of fun to hear the different voices of the fans depending on the location, and to see whether there were more men or more women today.
It was really nice. Since the cheering has become a real gold mine, I can feel that the fans' hearts are more energetic than before.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Let's start off with this time's uploads.
Morning Musume。 23 new member lesson video
This is the last lesson video of the new members, which we will show you in 4 parts.
Please take a look.
They passed!
Congratulations!
You have been selected to join Morning Musume。
You have been accepted!
Congratulations!
We are pleased to announce that we have been accepted as a member of Morning Musume。
Thank you for your interest!
How do you like it now?
I'm a little bit
I mean, you have to be aware of the fact that
The amount of Copper is totally different.
I thought it was very important.
Afterwards
I felt differently about how tired I was afterwards.
That means I didn't do enough, right?
You have to do it by yourself.
You have to make yourself that way.
If you don't push yourself
You can't do it that way. People get used to it, and they're always doing things.
You can't expect yourself to be able to do more. You have to expect more from yourself.
In that sense, it's the role of an idol to expect more from yourself. It's also the mission of being an idol, and that's why Morning Musume was going to a festival called "Jupin Jam" even though the weather was so bad.
Morning Musume is going to perform at a festival called Jupin Jam, and they're going to be on stage for about 40 minutes.
But...
But it's probably not too hot today, so we're going to perform for 40 minutes without drinking any water.
And we're going to play every song as fast as we can. It's going to be windy and rainy.
But we don't want to make the audience happy, we want to make them happy.
We wanted to make them happy and let them know about Morning Musume。 I want to make them happy and let them know about Morning Musume。
So, those who are working so hard, can you do it with them?
First of all, do you want to do it?
If we don't ask ourselves that question, we won't be able to convey our message.
So the most important thing is whether you really want to dance and whether you really like singing.
If you don't have the biggest part of you, you won't be able to continue, and you won't be able to continue because of all the hard things you have to do.
Even if you're having a hard time, even if you're angry, even if you can't do it, you say you want to do it because you absolutely love to dance and sing.
It's really obvious. Don't say it's obvious.
That's the best part.
And you have to express that.
I want you to be fully aware of that.
I'm going to show you two songs that I've been practicing.
I want you to express that part of yourself the most.
Yeah!
I'm also going to show you something about communicating.
A show with a lot of live dancing.
I'm lonely in love
And I want it.
But I have to be
This point of mine
It's not a lie.
Say it. I'm angry.
Blowing in the heat, solution
No one can solve it
Not even you, with your symphonies.
I can't do it now
Even love
I felt a sense of urgency.
I felt a kind of urgency
The fate of this love
Ta-tah, ta-tah, ta-tah.
It's true.
That's what I meant.
So, when we do the flow, we're both on the edge, right?
You have to dance with the person next to you as if you're destined to be together, otherwise it won't work.
If there were 12 people in the room, someone would get hurt if you showed off just a little bit.
So you want to be that focused and trust your partner at the very last minute.
You have to make eye contact.
You have to be able to look them in the eye to communicate with them.
I'm just barely making it, just barely making it as best I can.
too much shinanai
Thank you for watching.
No one will notice.
I can't do that.
I'm alone.
I'm not afraid of anything.
But you'll still be with someone.
I'm not going to force you to turn over.
I don't give a shit.
Bought it for me.
Pocky Image Solution.
Someday I'm sure it won't be
Love's favorite missusage
I know, I know, I know
This kindness of yoursThis kindness of yours.
But now you're forcing it.
Put on a good face! Last one!
Yes, OK!
I have to be honest and say that I am changing a bit more.
As for dancing, of course, I was a beginner at first.
Inoue was a beginner, and he couldn't remember the choreography, but he is improving, but...
I honestly think that they could have done a little more in the area of expression.
But I felt that both dancers were doing their best.
As today's lesson, I learned that it is important to be a good dancer, but it is also important to be able to convey one's feelings to one's partner.
I thought that many times my feelings are not conveyed, so before I dance well, I want to dance while thinking about the meaning of the lyrics.
Today's dance lesson made me realize that I am still far from perfection,
I think that what I learned in this lesson will not be in vain, so I will practice at home and after I pass the competition, I hope to be a member of Morning Musume。 I hope to practice at home and become a member of Morning Musume。
I learned not only technical skills but also the importance of self-assertion and other things from my teacher, so I will not forget that.
I can already feel the tension in the video.
But when I was taking the lessons, I was really struggling to learn the choreography, so I don't know what to say about the choreography first.
So I was just trying to learn the choreography first, and the expression in the video was just a part of that.
So I was just trying to learn the choreography first, and then I would start learning the expressions like this video.
I think it's because the two of us were able to do it together.
I think it's because of the two of you that you were able to teach me like this from the very beginning.
I was also surprised at the way you used the microphone.
But both of them have really developed their technique.
I'm looking forward to seeing more of them.
We haven't had any lessons together yet, so I'm really looking forward to working with them.
I'm looking forward to working with them.
I think that if we double the price with the other members, things will suddenly get a bit confusing.
So I'm really looking forward to the future in that respect as well.
Yes, I think it was the last thing that the girl with the bow hair said, but she was saying that what she had just learned was not in vain. I think this is the hardest time for you, but if you work hard now, you will be great later on.
If you work hard now, I'm sure you'll be able to see a future where you'll be able to enjoy performing.
That's all for now. 23 new member lesson video.
Angelem Rousousousen on sale now!
Anjelm Rousousousen on sale now!
You're working so hard, you're so cool!
Here is the next one.
Tsubaki Factory: Continuation of Shichibunsaki Vocal Recording
Tsubaki Factory's music from the continuation of Shichibunsaki,
Here's a look at the vocal recording by Shiori Yagi and Marin Fukuda.
Let's start with the A melody. She's a little bit tough, kind of cute.
Let's do it then. Please do.
Gumshoe, the loose end. Let me play with your fingertips.
Boring spring. What do you say?
Embarrassing gross. Pretending I didn't hear you.
It's the best I can do.
Great!
Can you make it a little sadder?
The base is fine, but I'd like to add a bit more sadness to it.
Let's try it again.
Let's play with the shells of the gumshiro with our fingertips.
What a boring spring.
I'm embarrassed to pretend I didn't hear the cross
It's the best I can do.
OK, let's continue.
I'll go on with the rest.
I can't remember who I was seeing last year.
sakura sakura mochi dough
Hey, is this going to end like this?
sunday rain night
Oh, Mae's Mae. Just go for the self voice one time next time.
It's about Mae.
Oh, it's "Mae," "Mae," "Mae," "Mae," "Mae.
What do you mean, "this is a self voice"?
Is that Fal?
Oh, meh, yoo-hoo.
More like a voice.
Mae.
Mae yoo-hoo.
Try it at that level.
Oh, Mae Yoo-hoo.
Mae Yoo-hoo.
Oh, Mae Yoo-Hoo.
Oh, mae yoo-hoo.
Cherry blossoms, cherry blossoms. It's almost the season.
Hey, is this gonna end like this?
It's gonna rain on Sunday.
Yeah, this one might be better.
I'll just get another one for the last song.
It's raining on Sunday
It's gonna be hard.
Okay, let's go to the next one.
The first chorus.
It's raining today, Sunday.
I think it's time you took me with you.
"Seven minutes to go...
I don't know if I'm in love with someone who knows I'm in love with you.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
I'll be your girlfriend.
Why are you being so blunt?
What color is it?
I see.
I think that's a good idea.
I just need to make the rhythm a little smoother.
And I'd like to make the landing of the last one a little cleaner.
Color.
If it rains, it won't go with the song.
I'd like to make it a little prettier.
Why are you messing around?
It's a color.
I want to feel the rhythm of it.
Okay, let's go a little further.Okay, well, let's go a little further.
It's raining today, Sunday.
I think it's time to take me there.
Seven Minutes Ahead.
I don't know if I'm in love with someone who's already in love with me.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
I'll be your girlfriend.
Why are you being so blunt?
What color is it?
Okay... you've got it all on tape.
Okay, we're done.
Thank you very much.
Let's start with the A melody. Let's go a little bit sad.
A little bit like a line.
Yes.
It's a bit far-fetched to say, "You always meet new people, don't you?
I don't mean to be snide, but it's a little bit like you're jealous.
Try to express that in your song.
Okay.
Okay, take 1.
What have you been up to? I heard you're changing jobs.
You're always meeting new people.
That's line three.
I guess I'm going to have to go to Falu.
Let's mix it up a bit.
You always meet new people.
I'm always meeting new people
Yes, I do.
Run'n's
You're always meeting new people
You're always making new friends
Rundown
You meet someone
I can keep going.
Rundown
Yes, you can.
Ruh-roh.
It's like a little bit of a hum.
Rundown
Ruh-roh...
Yeah, try it like that.
Okay, one more time.
What have you been up to? I heard you're going back to work. You're always meeting new people.
Yeah, I had some good points. I'm gonna leave this here.
Let's continue.
You're always meeting new people.
A season drenched in anticipation and hope
Hey, we're going home.
But it's my favorite place.
I'm trying to keep the image like that, but I don't want it to bounce around too much.
Maybe still a little too much.
Yes, that's about right.
Are you leaving like this?
But my favorite part.
OK!
So, let's finally get to the rusty part, shall we?
Yes, let's go to the chorus.
Take 1
But I like it
It's so frustratingly scorched
the sand of a fragile tree
I can't, can't, can't even act like it
I can't do it, I can't do it
I don't love you
I don't love you, I don't love you
A crush I feel only for you
Yeah, maybe I don't need to make the key too small.
I think I'll just go with the flow of "Tokimeki" as it is.
Tokimeki
OK.
Also, the wings are a little weak,
I'd like to make the rhythm a little more steady.
Let's write it down. Take 5.
I can't even say it.
I don't love you, I don't love you, I don't love you,
I'm not in love with you, I'm not in love with you, but I feel a crush that I feel only for you.
Yes, OK.
Yes, done!
Thank you very much.
Yes, you two are really good.
As soon as I saw the video, I thought, "What? Too good? I said, "Too good?
Especially, I, Marin Fukuda, was in the first tour of Kachofugetsu after I joined the company,
I was on the same team with Marin Fukuda at Kacho Fugetsu.
I saw how she sang in the beginning, so I thought it was really wonderful to see how she has grown up and become a singer.
But both of them have slightly different views of the world. They have the same view of the world, but they are slightly different within that view,
I felt that the director knew that, and it was a way of recording that was very different from Morning's way, so I really enjoyed watching it.
I was really inspired by the recording videos of other groups,
I was really impressed by the clarity and transparency of their voices.
Also, the lyrics of the song "Seventh Blossom" are very beautiful, and the lyrics are very deep,
I thought the lyrics were quite difficult to understand and it would take me a long time to understand them,
I thought the lyrics were rather difficult to understand, but I could feel that both of them were filled with great emotion, and I could feel their feelings,
I am very much looking forward to hearing this song at concerts and other occasions in the future.
This is a continuation of the vocal recording of "Camellia Factory: Seventh Blossom".
You can do it!
Rio Kitagawa of Morning Musume。 23's Rio Kitagawa and
Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume。 23's Rio Sakurai Rio delivers the up-dated paper.
Here is the next one!
Beyonce - Yume to Dake no Yozora ni Dakunai Yozora ni Musical Instrumental Recording
From Beyonce's newest single, "Yume to Yonderu Yozora no Yume wo Kakurenai Yozora ni
Please take a look at the piano recording by Kobayashi Gonaka!Please take a look at the piano recording of Mr. Kobayashi.
Yes, Mr. Kobayashi, can you hear me? I can hear you. I'm Kato, the arranger. I look forward to working with you. Please take care of it.
The atmosphere of the music itself gradually changes during the song, but at first, the arrangement is more like an accompaniment for a chorus,
After the introduction, a march-like brass band starts. Then, after the introduction, a march-like brass band starts, and finally the music ends up with a rather cool jazz big band-like atmosphere.
I would appreciate it if you could change the piano to express that kind of feeling in a rather exaggerated way.
Okay, then, let's go. Please do.
I won't let the night sky where you can't even dream
I'll walk humming to the melody you love
I won't let the night sky be a place where you can't even sing of love
me
It's wonderful that you were born as you
I thought it could be like this, even with the atmosphere of the beginning of the song, the intro 2
I wanted the groove to be a little more positive and upbeat, so that the audience could hear the whole orchestra.
I thought it would be better if I could take the groove to a more positive and groovy direction.
Thank you for listening!
I won't let the night sky where you can't even dream
While humming the melody you like
I want to walk
I want to be loved
I can't sing, I won't let it be the night sky
It's wonderful that you were born as you
Hey, I can't sing, I won't let it be the night sky
What's the glissando in the intro and the last part?
I wonder if they use thumbnail glissandos now.
It's a little too fast.
A little quicker.
I'd like to do it a little faster.
Is it easier to do the glissando with your fingernail?
Yes, yes, I can't use it too much because it comes up many times in a song.
I think the current one is a little too slow in terms of momentum,
If I could go faster with those fingernails, it would be the hardest in terms of sound, and it would have more power, but....
I understand.
giraffe
Yes, I think this is the best one so far.
I think this is the best one so far.
How do you like it?
Now, let's start from the top again.
I won't let the night sky become a place where you can't even dream.
So many stars love you
I can't draw anything, I can't believe the time
I'll never forget that I was born on such a beautiful star
Thank you, I'm sorry, take care, bye-bye
I hugged the beautiful stars one step ahead of you
In my heart
I messed up on the A-dash...
I guess I'll start with 1A dash...
I think the B was good, but how did you feel when you played it?
I put my heart into it.
That's great... much better than before.
Okay, let's start at the beginning of the 1A dash.
Play it from the beginning of the 1A dash to about the first note of B.
Yes, sir.
I can't paint a picture of this incredible time.
I forgot where I was born on this beautiful planet.
Thank you.
Yes, yes, yes, it's beautiful, it's wonderful, it's perfect.
Let's go to 3C.
vert 2
I think we're getting to the right place. I think what you're trying to do is right.
I think what you're trying to do is the right thing, and it's okay if it's a little rough and loose.
I think what you're trying to do is the right thing.
So I think I'm trying to become a pianist who is not serious by nature.
Also, I think it's important to have fun while thinking of the faces of the people who are singing.
Yes.
The first time I said your name was Lalala.
No one in this world is watching the sky
Someday you'll live again, and we'll want to find you
Lalalalalalala, we'll find you
Someday we'll live again and we'll find you
It's got a great vibe. I think it's good. Are you okay with that? I think it's great.
I think it's great.
Okay, we're done with the piano recording.
I really look forward to every piano recording.
But this time, what was difficult was...
I had to play with a classical touch and listen to the notes very carefully.
I had to listen to the accompaniment and other orchestra members' voices.
I had to play in accordance with the members' voices and tones.
But as the second half of the song goes on, it becomes more jazz-like
But as the second half of the song progresses, it starts to sound more jazz-like
like a pop song played on an electronic piano.
I have to play with a groove like a pop musician playing on an electronic piano.
As a pianist, it was very difficult for me.
I think it was very difficult for me as a pianist to play this piece.
When you listen to this song
In terms of the piano, there are some parts that are played in a classical style and others in a jazz style.
I want you to hear the change in tone from the classical style to the jazz style.
I want the listener to hear the change in tone when I play it in a classical style and when I play it in a jazz style.
When I play the piano in a classical style, I want the audience to hear how it sounds and how it comes out.
When I play in a classical style, I listen to how it sounds and how it comes out, but when I play in a jazz style
But when I play jazz style, I have to listen to how it sounds and how it's played.
I think the groove and the touch of your fingers are very different.
Even if you look at this video of the recording, you can see how I play from above.
You can see how he plays from the top and how he listens to the notes with his fingertips.
I think you can see the difference in the way he plays.
I think you can see the difference.
I want you to pay attention to the touch and the tone.
When I first heard "This Dream I Can't Even Draw", I thought it was really sparkling.
There are a lot of sounds in it, and they gradually get louder and louder until it becomes a very grand piece of music at the end.
In the end, I thought it was a very grand music, and within the music, there was Mr. Kobayashi's wonderful piano tone.
I think you can actually see Mr. Kobayashi playing this piece at the concert.
I was also able to see him play the piano at the concert, and I thought, "If it were me, I wouldn't be able to play the piano at a concert like this.I have actually seen it, and I think that playing the piano in a concert hall like this would be a dream come true for me.
I would never be able to actually play the piano. I don't think I would ever get to actually play the piano.
I was thinking how wonderful Mr. Kobayashi was, so now that I have the opportunity to see him perform, I have a lot of respect for him.
I was really impressed by the way he played the first time, and the director was trying to make it better, but from our point of view, it was just too much from the very first shot,
But it was really impressive to see Mr. Kobayashi enjoying the recording process so much, and we could really feel how much he loves the piano,
I could really feel that Mr. Kobayashi's power made this song more and more magnificent and brought it more and more to life,
I'm looking forward to seeing many more piano recordings by Mr. Kobayashi. I'm watching a lot of piano recordings by Mr. Kobayashi and the two of them.
I hope to see many more of them in the future.
That's all for now, Beyonce, I can't even draw a dream in the night sky was Honoka Kobayashi's piano recording.
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't.
I wouldn't kiss you with a leven chauffeur
Even to you, I couldn't spoil you
Pride Bright July 12 On Scion
I am always on your side.
It's time to say goodbye to the up-dated paper that Rio Shimokawa and Rio Sakurai have been presenting!
We've seen a lot of different videos this time, but the one that left the biggest impression on me, Sakurai, was...
I was impressed by Tsubaki Factory's vocal recording of "Seventh Blossom".
I think I've introduced their recording video in this newsletter.
Both of them really conveyed the emotion of the lyrics to me.
It's a really beautiful song, so I thought it would be very difficult for me to interpret the lyrics.
I thought it would be very difficult for me to interpret the lyrics of the song because it is so beautiful.
I, Kitagawa, was impressed by the video of the dance lesson of the 17th term.
I was really impressed by the video of the dance lesson of the 17th term, and I could really feel how they were working so hard.
I really want to cheer them on as I watch the video.
We haven't met the members that much yet, but as we work together, I'm sure things will change.
I'm really looking forward to the future, and I can't wait to perform with them.
In UpCami, we'll take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
We'll be introducing you to the parts you don't normally get to see, so please subscribe to our channel! This time, up-cam's partner is Rio Kitagawa of Morning Musume。 23's Rio Kitagawa and
Morning Musume。 23. Good bye.
Next time on Upokami!
The making of the music video "Alumni of ANGELUM"!
And
Beyonce, Seek Me! The recording session of Beyonce: The Fateful Traveler will be shown on the website.
We hope you enjoy it!
Please subscribe to our channel!